=My Sweet Professor= =Episode 23=
= أستاذي الحلو = = الحلقة 23 =
You dropped this
لقد أسقطت هذا
yesterday.
في الامس.
And,
و،
when you were in custody
عندما كنت في الحجز
eight years ago,
منذ ثماني سنوات،
Huo Shang actually talked to me.
هوو شانغ تحدث معي بالفعل.
Hey, you're so pretty.
انت جميلة جدا.
Add me to your contacts on WeChat.
أضفني إلى جهات الاتصال الخاصة بك على WeChat.
Don't touch me. Go away!
لا تلمسني.  يبتعد!
Liang Qi!
ليانغ تشي!
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
It's
إنه
none of your business!
هذا ليس من شأنك!
Gao Yuan!
جاو يوان!
Mind your own business!
اهتم بشؤونك الخاصة!
Go away!
يبتعد!
Leave me alone!
اتركني وحدي!
What should I do? Help me!
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟  ساعدني!
Liang Qi,
ليانغ تشي ،
no matter who asks you about this,
بغض النظر عمن يسألك عن هذا ،
just tell them it's me.
فقط أخبرهم أنه أنا.
In fact, that punk was not hurt at that time.
في الواقع ، هذا الشرير لم يصب بأذى في ذلك الوقت.
He just fainted.
لقد أغمي عليه للتو.
But he called some other punks
لكنه دعا بعض الأشرار الأخرى
and claimed that they were gonna take their revenge on us.
وادعوا أنهم سينتقمون منا.
Huo Shang knew about this.
علم Huo Shang بهذا.
He hit him badly.
ضربه ضربا مبرحا.
He was also seriously wounded.
كما أصيب بجروح خطيرة.
Hello? 110?
مرحبًا؟  110
I need to turn myself in.
أنا بحاجة إلى تسليم نفسي.
The reason why you were free to go
سبب كونك حرًا في الذهاب
(Hexi Detention Center) was that the police found out later
(مركز احتجاز Hexi) هو أن الشرطة اكتشفت ذلك لاحقًا
that you didn't hit that man.
أنك لم تضرب ذلك الرجل.
It's OK. It's all over.
كل شيء على مايرام.  إنتهى الأمر.
Mom.
أم.
Mm.
مم.
Is this really over?
هل هذا حقا انتهى؟
Rest assured. It's all over.
اطمئن، لا تشغل بالك.  إنتهى الأمر.
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Huo Shang turned himself in
سلم هوه شانغ نفسه
later.
في وقت لاحق.
Hey, Dr. Gao.
مرحبًا ، دكتور جاو.
Mr. Huo sends me to give you this.
السيد هوو يرسل لي لأعطيك هذا.
Congratulations on your wedding.
مبروك على حفل الزفاف الخاص بك.
In fact,
في الواقع،
there's some reason that Mr. Huo didn't answer your calls.
هناك سبب لعدم رد السيد هوو على مكالماتك.
He was afraid that he might be your burden.
كان خائفًا من أن يكون عبئًا عليك.
Take me to see him. Now.
خذني لرؤيته.  حاليا.
Get in my car.
اركب سيارتي.
♪ Some friends are drifting apart ♪
♪ بعض الأصدقاء يتباعدون ♪
♪ Some wishes can't be true ♪
♪ بعض الأمنيات لا يمكن أن تكون حقيقية ♪
♪ When the car drove away that day ♪
عندما ابتعدت السيارة في ذلك اليوم ♪
♪ We tried our best to run and chase the summer ♪
♪ لقد بذلنا قصارى جهدنا للركض ومطاردة الصيف ♪
♪ But still miss it ♪
♪ لكن ما زلت أفتقدها ♪
=My Sweet Professor=
= أستاذي الحلو =